<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Censor Census</string>
    <string name="actionBarTitle">Censorship Monitoring Project</string>
    <string name="actionBarSubtitle">Making censorship accountable</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Wireless Config</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Request Config</string>
    <string name="title_section3">ORG / OONI Signup</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Statistics</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_add">Test a Link</string>
    <string name="action_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="action_gencert">Generate Client Certificate</string>

    <string name="warningTitle">WARNING: READ BEFORE USE</string>
    <string name="warningMessage">IT IS STRONGLY RECOMMENDED YOU DO NOT USE THIS APP UNLESS YOU FULLY UNDERSTAND THE IMPLICATIONS\n\nIf you click "I agree" this app will possibly receive URLs that lead to censored or illegal content.\n\nThe app will only make a HTTP HEAD request so content (legal or otherwise) should not be downloaded (as per RFC2616) but there is still the possibility of repercussions.\n\nBy agreeing to use this app you indemnify the author of any liability.\n\nThis program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.</string>
    <string name="warningAgree">I Agree</string>
    <string name="warningExit">No, Exit!</string>
    <string name="warningAgreed">Thank you for helping to make the Internet more accountable!</string>

    <!-- Fragment ORG -->
    <string name="orgIntro">If you would also like to participate in the Open Rights Group Censorship Monitoring Project ( http://bit.ly/18B4e8Y ) you will need to signup and configure your device as a probe.</string>
    <string name="orgUnavailable">THIS FEATURE IS UNAVAILABLE AT THE MOMENT</string>

    <!--Fragment - Wireless -->
    <string name="wirelessMessage">To better profile which ISPs are censoring and which aren\'t it would be useful to have meta data about the ISP used to check URLs.\n\nBy volunteering this information it will give a clearer picture of the scope of censorship.</string>
    <string name="wirelessNew">This WiFi network hasn\'t been seen before, which ISP does it use?</string>

    <!-- Fragment - Check Config -->
    <string name="checkConfigFheckBoxLabel">Receive URL check requests and process them automatically</string>
</resources>
